{
    "subject": "resource/Arthur_Wagner",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:People_educated_at_Eton_College",
    "human_readable": "Arthur Wagner is a subject of Category:People educated at Eton College.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8223126530647278,
            "question": "What category does Arthur Wagner belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7856194972991943,
            "question": "Who is Arthur Wagner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7652649879455566,
            "question": "Where did Arthur Wagner receive his education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6690514087677002,
            "question": "Is there any information about Arthur Wagner's career or accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6661862730979919,
            "question": "How does Arthur Wagner's education potentially influence his future endeavors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5296587944030762,
            "question": "What are some characteristics commonly associated with people educated at prestigious institutions like Eton College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295877456665039,
            "question": "Are there any connections between Arthur Wagner and other individuals mentioned in this context?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37253621220588684,
            "question": "Name a famous person who also attended Eton College."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29735347628593445,
            "question": "Can you name other notable alumni of Eton College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2947448492050171,
            "question": "What types of institutions are considered part of the Category:People?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Arthur Wagner is a subject of Category:People educated at Eton College.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2224_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other notable alumni of Eton College?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2224_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous person who also attended Eton College.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2224_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any connections between Arthur Wagner and other individuals mentioned in this context?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2224_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2224_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nNone of the documents mention Arthur Wagner attending Eton College. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: None of the provided documents mention Arthur Wagner being educated at Eton College. The documents discuss Arthur Douglas Wagner in relation to his career as an educator and leader in theater, but there is no information about his education that would suggest he attended Eton College."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Arthur Wagner is not mentioned as having attended Eton College in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text details Arthur Wagner's education at Trinity College, Cambridge.  It makes no mention of Eton College.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Arthur Wagner being educated at Eton College in the provided context information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Arthur Wagner being educated at Eton College. It only provides details about his education at Trinity College, Cambridge, and Earlham College, as well as his achievements in the field of theater and clergy.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}